http://www.mbk1.com/privacy-policy.html

Print This PageEmail This Page
Contact Us
Contact Information Directions Phone Directory Employment
Privacy PolicyLast modified: April 19, 2016MBK Tape Solutions respects your privacy and our site visitors' information. We do not sell or rent to third parties any of the information collected via this website.Information Collected
If you request or submit information to us by sending an Email or by filling out a "contact" form, we may save your Email address as well as any other information you provide on website forms submitted to us. This information may be used to contact you in the future by mail, Email, or phone to convey information about our products, services or solutions that we feel may benefit you. Information Collected by Others
This notice addresses only MBK Tape Solutions' website policy, and does not apply to sites that users access via links from our site. MBK Tape Solutions is not responsible for the information collecting policies of other sites, for the practices employed by websites linked to or from our website, or for the information or content contained therein. Often, links to other websites are provided solely on the basis that they may contain useful information for our website visitors. Users are advised to review the privacy policies of these other websites.Cookies
This website may set cookies on your computer. A cookie is a text file that is placed on your computer by our web server and helps recall your use of this website. Cookies are uniquely generated and assigned to you.We may also use one or more 3rd party tracking tools that utilize data collected to track and examine the use of www.mbktape.com and to prepare reports regarding our website's usage. These 3rd party tracking tools do not collect personally identifiable information.Other Information We Collect
MBK Tape Solutions may keep track of technical information about your computer or mobile device, such as the browser type and version, browser plug-in types and versions and operating system of your computer; the Internet Service Provider (ISP) or other provider you use to access this website, links on this website and certain of our services; and your internet protocol (IP) address, location and time zone setting. To help us understand the use of this website by users, improve your site experience and aid us in marketing and managing this website and our services, we may also collect information as to how you were directed to this website and our services, how you navigate around them, what products or services you browse, which external websites or links you access from this website. This information may be used, among other things, in the reporting, marketing and analysis of this website and its services and features and may be shared with our affiliates, suppliers, providers and/or their and our respective agents and contractors. Updating, Correcting, and Deleting Personal Information
If you would like to have your personal information updated, corrected or removed from our records, please us send an Email with "Update/Correct or Remove personal information" in the subject line to info@mbktape.com.Opting Out Of Email
You can choose to opt out of receiving email from MBK Tape Solutions at any time. MBK Tape Solutions markets some of its own products and services by email. Every email sent from MBK Tape Solutions will include appropriate unsubscribe instructions. Opting out of email offers for a specific MBK Tape Solutions service only opts you out of that service. To opt out of all email marketing messages from MBK Tape Solutions, you must send an email to info@mbktape.com from the email address you wish to unsubscribe. Please clearly state in your email, "Unsubscribe me from all MBK Tape Solutions email marketing." This is the only way to assure that you no longer receive email advertising messages from MBK Tape Solutions.Data Security
We use reasonable precautions to keep user information disclosed to us secure. To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy and ensure the appropriate use of information, we have put in place commercially reasonable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect.We may disclose information we collect to third parties, under contract to us, as required to operate this website, provide certain services or features offered by this website or to perform business functions on our behalf. We will only release this information to those companies that we believe to be responsible. However, we are not responsible for any breach of security or for any actions of any third parties who receive the information. Also, once information has been provided to a third party, it is out of the control of MBK Tape Solutions and subject to the policies of that third party.Children
This website is not intended for use by children, and the terms and conditions governing the use of this website and its features require that you must be at least 18 years old to use them.Legally Compelled Disclosure of Information
MBK Tape Solutions may disclose information when legally compelled to do so: when we, in good faith, believe that the law requires us to do so or for the protection of our legal rights.Periodic Policy Changes
Please note that MBK Tape Solutions reviews its privacy practices from time-to-time (i.e. to track technology and/or legal changes), and that these practices are subject to change. To ensure continuing familiarity with the most current version of our privacy policy, please bookmark and periodically review this page.This policy statement is made in the name of MBK Tape Solutions and is effective as of the date last modified as noted above. This statement does not create an agreement between MBK Tape Solutions and users, and as such, does not create any legal rights for any party.Contact Us:
MBK Tape Solutions
9959 Canoga Avenue
Chatsworth, CA 91311
Toll Free: 818-998-1477
Direct: 818-998-1477
Fax: 818-998-6059
Email: info@mbktape.com
Website: www.mbktape.com
Navigation
TAPES & MATERIALS
Adhesive Transfer Tape Single Sided Tape Double Sided Tape Cloth Tape & Nonwovens Films & Film Tape Foams & Foam Tape Foils & Foil Tape Paper Tape Rubber Tape Hook & Loop Fasteners Release Liners Other Materials Finished Goods
Medical Tapes & Materials
Adhesive Transfer Tapes Single Coated Tapes Double Coated Tapes Films & Film Tapes Foams & Foam Tapes Nonwovens & Wovens Hydrogels & Hydrocolloids Medical Grade Silicones Release Liners
SPECIALTY TAPES
Medical Tape - Stick to Skin FDA Food Contact Tape Removable Tape Transparent Tape Reflective Tape Anti Slip Tape Slick Surface Tape Low Surface Energy Tape UL Rated Tape Flame Retardant Tape Low Outgassing Tape Eco-Friendly Tape
TAPE APPLICATIONS
Attachment & Bonding Tape Dampening Tape Decorative Tape Electrical Tape Industrial Tape Laminating Material Marking Tape Masking Tape Medical Tape Packaging Tape Protective Tape Safety Tape Security Tape Sealing Tape & Gaskets Splicing Tape Strapping Tape Thermal Tape
INDUSTRIES SERVED
Aerospace & Defense Architecture & Construction Electronics & Electrical Entertainment & Hospitality Food, Beverages & Pharma Graphic Arts & Display Health Care & Wearables Manufacturing Packaging & Printing Personal Care & Consumer Recreation Renewable Energy Transportation
Services
Die-Cutting Services Laminating Services Printing Services Rewinding Services Sheeting Services Slitting Services Spooling & Reeling Services Packaging & Product Fulfilment
Clean Room ManufacturingContract ManufacturingProduct DevelopmentQuality Assurance
CATALOG
Search by Material Search by Medical Material Search by Application Search by Attributes Search by Industry Search Finished Goods Search by Brands
RESOURCES
Glossary Literature Videos Manufacturing Partners Converter Partners: 3M Converter Partners: Avery Dennison Converter Partners: Mactac Converter Partners: Tesa Tapes Converter Partners: Vancive
ABOUT US
Company Profile What is Converting Why Choose MBK MBK History Awards & Partners Payment Forms
NEWS
Trade shows & Events Blog, News & Press Releases
MBK Company News MBK Partners News Lean Manufacturing Industrial Products Medical Products Wearables Food Contact Products
Spotlight Products & Applications
REQUEST FORMS
Request Literature Request a Sample Request Custom Quote Place an Order Delivery Questions
CONTACT US
Contact Information Directions Phone Directory Employment
PRIVACY POLICY
Privacy Policy  |  Sitemap  |  Catalog Index© 2019, MBK Tape Solutions  |  Site created by Thomas Web Solutions and powered by Navigator Platform
